Life can change in a heartbeat.
Then She Found Me is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Helen Hunt.
A New York schoolteacher experiences a midlife crisis when, in quick succession, her husband leaves, her adoptive mother dies, and her biological mother,
an eccentric talk show host, materializes and turns her life upside down as she begins a courtship with the father of one of her students.
April Epner, played by Helen Hunt.
Bernice Graves, played by Bette Midler.
Frank, played by Colin Firth.
Ben Green, played by Matthew Broderick.
Dr. Freddy Epner, played by Ben Shenkman.
Trudy Epner, played by Lynn Cohen.
Then She Found Me is a 2007 American comedy drama film directed by Helen Hunt.
The screenplay by Hunt, Alice Arlen, and Victor Levin is very loosely
based on the 1990 novel of the same name by Elinor Lipman.
The film marked Hunt's feature film directorial debut.
The film explores themes of new york city, adoption,
woman director, adopted daughter.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.